const verbal=[
{
	question:"THRUST:SPEAR"
	options:['mangle:iron','fence:epee','scabbard:sword'],
	answer:'fence:epee'
},
{
	question:"LIGHT:BLIND"
	options:['speech:dumb','language:deaf','voice:vibration'],
	answer:'speech:dumb'
},
{
	question:"Fate smiles ...... those who untiringly grapple with stark realities of life."
	options:['with','on','over'],
	answer:'on'
},
{
	question:" I saw a ...... of cows in the field."
	options:['group','herd','swarm'],
	answer:'herd'
},
{
	question:"To err is ...... to forgive divine."
	options:['human','beastly','inhuman'],
	answer:'human'
},
{
	question:"Find the correctly spelt words"
	options:['Efficient','Treatmeant','Beterment'],
	answer:'Efficient'
},
{
	question:"Find the correctly spelt words."
	options:['Ommineous','Ominous','Omineous'],
	answer:'Ominous'
},
{
	question:"choose the word which best expresses the meaning of CORPULENT."
	options:['Lean','Emaciated','Obese'],
	answer:'Obese'
},
{
	question:"choose the word which best expresses the meaning of the given word"
	options:['Pull','Free','Complicate'],
	answer:'Free'
},
{
	question:"choose the one which can be substituted for the sentence 'That which cannot be corrected'."
	options:['Unintelligible','Incorrigible','Illegible'],
	answer:'Incorrigible'
}]